So we're going to be everywhere tonight.
And, you know, listen, I understand that,
um, sometimes Bible studies can
become a little bit redundant, you know, we can kind of
lose our way and, uh, you know, again, I told you
about the study and and Daniel and how,
you know, a sweet lady in the church came up and asked, when are we going to be done?
And I thought she was saying like, you know, hey, as long as it
takes, because it's so good, and what she was really saying is, I'm bored.
Can we hear about something else?
And so I understand, you know, when we talk
about something like the end times, there's a lot that goes into
it, and even with taking our time, we're on less
than 11 in this study, but even with taking our
time, there's so much more that we can learn.
So I just want us to appreciate the fact that if it's in the Bible, we ought to know it.
I mean, let's think about that for a second.
If it's in the Bible, it's very simple.
We ought to know it.
So after several weeks away from our study, we're back in it tonight.
Uh, we were going to look at what is going to happen during the seven-year tribulation.
We were going to start looking at the 7 trumpets,
uh, and I say, you know,
what we know, because there are details given
to us, but there's also much speculation that can
cause an inaccurate and uninformed opinion of
what exactly is going to happen.
It is amazing to me, and really, we see it in scripture, um,
you know, being warned about, but it's amazing to me how some people can
look at the same text and interpret such different things.
For example, I had a conversation today about baptism,
about Lord's Supper, the frequency of it, this baptism saved, and,
you know, the person I was talking to, I believe genuinely loves Jesus.
But we look at the same text and we do not
come out the same way.
Does that make sense?
And so the end times is very similar to that.
It is important to understand that it's okay to have opinion, though.
Right?
When you should have an opinion about God's word based on God's word.
You need to know not just what you believe but why you believe it.
There's a lot of people in the church that know what they believe.
They love to tell you what they believe, but they don't know why they believe it, right?
They say, well, I just, you know, this is what I've been taught.
Well, well, show me, you know, chapter and verse and let's talk about it some more.
Let's learn something new.
Let's learn something more.
Not that there's a new interpretation, but let's make sure we're in line with the text.
Some people, and I know that this might be a trigger word for some people,
but in my circle, we call it wrestling with the text.
We've got to make sure that we are in line with
what God's word says, but we must keep it.
If there's not strict uh, immediate,
obvious and evident command or principle given.
You better understand, we better differentiate opinion from doctrine.
Does that make any sense?
Once we create supposed truth that we cannot back up with
scripture, we are navigating choppy waters.
In other words, when someone tells you what they believe, and
they say, well, based on this, I just feel like.
But I don't really care what you feel like based on scripture.
I mean, I don't mean to sound mean, but what I'm saying is when
I read scripture, it convicts me.
For example, on Sunday, when we preached about devotion to each
other, I made 2 phone calls right at the church, why?
Because I got convicted.
The word that I was preaching to the flock that
I'd studied all week for, it spoke to me as I
was speaking to you and it didn't make me feel good, but it called me to action.
Listen, God's word is not going to always make you feel good.
But it's going to get you to where you should be.
And there's nothing better.
There's a no better feeling than being right with God.
You understand what I'm saying?
There's no better position in the world than being right with God.
In other words, if a preacher, a teacher claims to know exactly what is going to
happen with all the details, including timeline and all, I can assure
you, 2 things.
One or 2 things about this person is true.
Either they are arrogant or ignorant.
Or both.
But I'm not, again, both of which is unfortunate.
So let's make sure that we properly differentiate
between speculation and scripture.
So what do we know about this seven-year tribulation so far in this study?
Now, again, we're looking at this from a pre-tribulation view,
although we have in depth gone over the other views and they all have valid points.
I've told you before, listen, that's not a salvation issue.
I'm going to heaven.
How I get there is through Jesus.
Everything else we can figure out.
When I do this, I'm just, I'm meaning something.
I'm going to do it a lot tonight because I feel uncomfortable being down here and not up there.
So it's just going to be what it is.
But so we got to understand, um,
that we are looking at a pre-tribulation view, okay?
God is going to call up the church, therefore removing the
protection of the church that the church brings to the earth.
I say protection because the Holy Spirit dwells within us.
People do not understand.
If you took the church away,
There is no limits to the evil in this world.
Now, I know we live in an evil world already, but there are churches
that do God's will.
There are churches that expand the kingdom of God.
There are churches.
You know, I believe we are a church that makes an impact for good,
that makes an impact for the gospel.
You take this away in our community.
becomes a lot darker.
You take the light away, the dark gets a lot darker.
And so we are here to fight the darkness with the light.
God is going to take much of that light away by rapturing the
church, and that is his plan.
But because of much of revelation is symbolic.
Many see Revelation 4, verse one through 2.
When God calls John up to heaven for the vision as a
symbol of God calling up the church.
Again, we can debate all this, but I'm just telling you what people
see this as.
So Revelations chapter 4, Revelation chapter 4, verse one and
2 after this, I looked, and behold, a door was opened in
heaven, and the 1st voice which I heard was, as it
were, of a trumpet talking with me, which say, come up hither, and
I will show these things, which must be hereafter.
And immediately I was in the spirit.
And behold, a throne was set in heaven and one
sat on the throne.
So we see that God calls John up,
whether that's a symbolic of the church or not, again, we're
looking at this in a pre-tribulation rapture perspective,
we also know that according to Daniel 9, verse 27,
the antichrist signs a covenant with a nation of
Israel, it says in verse 27 in that chapter, and he will make a
firm covenant with the many for one
week, but in the middle of the week, he will put a stop to sacrificing grain,
offering, and on the wing of abominations will come one who makes desolate, even until a complete
One that is decreed is poured out on
the one who makes desolate.
This is a seven-year covenant.
This covenant is one that promises world peace, one world government.
You know, you can buy and sell only if they say at
the halfway mark, which will be 3.5 years.
The Antichrist breaks this covenant.
And this is outlined in Revelation 6 with the seals, 7 seals being broken.
Now, between chapter 6 and 8, there is what can be called an
interlude or moment of pause.
This is when John writes of the 144,000
Jews and the multitude of martyrs in that chapter.
Now, I do want to clarify a couple things, and I'm
going to be honest with you, we're going to kind of camp out on 144,000.
I told you my plan when I sat down was to get to the trumpets
and we stopped at where we are in chapter 7.
But I pray, you know, I believe it's God's will for us to learn this.
So we're going to do that.
Okay?
before we do that, let's pray.
Father, we thank you, Lord, for this night.
God, we just thank you for just being able to gather together freely
to learn from your word, to worship the name of Jesus.
God, we just ask you that everything we do and say tonight is pleasing to you.
God, give us wisdom and discernment, God.
Uh, through the Holy Ghost God, to be able to discern what is right and wrong.
It's in Jesus name, pray.
Anybody said?
Um, so again, we see here, uh, There
are many things that are hotly and passionately debated in Revelation.
I mean, it is probably one of the most debated books in the Bible.
The 144,000 is one of these things.
So we're going to look at a text so we can get an understanding of what God's word
says about it 1st and foremost because really that's the most important thing.
So if you're in God's word, Revelation chapter seven, we're
going to read verses one through eight, if you're there, say read.
And after these things, I saw 4 angels standing
on the 4 corners of the earth.
Now, real quick, just to tell you where we are in the timeline, even though revelation is
not necessarily linear, is more of just events and it
kind of jumps around a little bit.
But it's after this 6 seals.
The 7th seal is the trumpets, right?
So we're 6 seals in, and then we get an interlude.
We get a moment of pause here.
Okay?
And after these things, I saw 4 angels standing on the 4 corners
of the earth, holding the 4 winds of the earth that the wind should
not blow on the earth, nor on the sea, nor on any tree.
And I saw another angel ascending from
the east, having the seal of the living God, and
he cried with a loud voice to the 4 angels to whom it was given to
hurt the earth and the sea, saying, hurt not the earth, neither
the sea, nor the trees, till we have sealed the
servants of our God in their foreheads.
And I heard a number of them, which were sealed.
And they were sealed 144,000 of all
the tribes of the children of Israel.
of the tribe of Judah, we're sealed 12,000, and
we don't have to read all that.
That's literally just it names each tribe, and it says 12,000 from that tribe, okay?
So for time's sake, we won't read all that, okay?
So we see here, there's a few details I'd like to emphasize.
First, we know that there is 144,000.
And they're derived from the nation of Israel.
Again, 12,000 is 12 tribes, 12,000 each,
that equals to 144,000.
Second, we know they are sealed.
Now, we know this is a protecting a protected
seal because the word and term seal here means.
It is such a deep word.
It says to put a seal on mark for possession
or identity, give in a secure manner, turnover,
deliver safely, but also to make
known and clearly show.
So it's a very, it's a very beautiful word here.
Now, looking at this definition, we
can see the truth in what we have already read, if you look again at
verse 2 and 3, and I saw another angel ascending from the east, having a seal
of the living God, and he cried aloud, voice to
the 4 angels, to whom it was given to hurt the earth and the sea, saying,
hurt not to see, neither the sea, nor the trees, till not
the earth, nor the sea, nor the trees, till we have sealed the
servants of our God in their forehead.
So we see here, if we look at the definition of what seal means,
That word still means to mark for identity to make clearly known.
Well, we see that John says that God puts some
sort of seal upon their foreheads.
In other words, they're clearly known for what their purpose is.
Their seal is evident.
We also know that this still serves as a way of deliverance and protection
from the events and destruction of the tribulation.
We see this in Revelation 14, one through 3.
And I looked, and lower lamb stood on the Mount Zion, and
with him 140 and 4,44,000,
having his father's name written in their foreheads.
And I heard a voice from heaven as the voice of many waters, and
the voice of a great thunder, and I heard the voice of harpers harping
with their hearts, and they sung, as it were, a new song before
the throne, and before the 4 beasts and the elders.
And no man could learn that song, but the 144,000,
which were redeemed from the earth.
It is obvious that whoever these sealed Jews are,
they're clearly known and protected
for a time such as this.
I want to take a moment to ponder on this with you.
And this is really where we get into application today because I
don't plan on being here, right, to see the 144.
I guess I might see them around the throne.
I not sure how that's going to work out.
But I know I believe I'm going to be caught up, you know what I'm saying?
Get a little head start to heaven.
But let's take a moment here.
The Bible interconnects like no other piece of literature the world has ever known.
You believe that?
I mean, there is a thread.
Uh, I forget exactly who it was.
Oh my goodness.
I forget exactly who it was, but he preached from
Genesis to Revelation.
It took 12 hours.
And it was called the Scarlet Thread of Redemption through the Bible.
It was awesome.
No, I did not listen to them.
But what I'm trying to say is every single, every single
thing God tells us, you can connect it somewhere because God's
plan has been in place for a long, long time.
All right, so you say, well, what are you talking about?
Remember that word seal, we just spent some time defining and explaining.
Amen?
Remember that word?
Okay.
John uses it here.
But Paul uses it somewhere else in the New Testament as well.
I'm hoping you know where I'm going with this.
Ephesians one, 13 through 14.
One of my favorite scriptures in all the Bible.
say that so much.
In whom ye also trusted.
After that ye heard the word of truth, the gospel of your salvation,
in whom also after that ye believed, look, you were sealed with
that Holy Spirit of promise.
Which is the earnest of our inheritance until the redemption of
the purchase possession unto the praise of his glory.
Now, if you're reading scripture, do
not depend on the English language.
Is that fair?
Because the Bible is not written in English.
Okay?
So there's a deeper language that we didn't know.
As a matter of fact, if you don't know how to, well, how do I know what the word says?
There's a thing called a blue letter Bible app, okay?
It's a very simple, nice little introductory
to Greek and Hebrew.
You can download it.
It's free on your phone.
You go to an interlinear concordinates,
and it tells you all the Greek, what it means, where it is and all stuff.
You got to get the blue letter Bible app, okay?
And I say that because when we see that word sealed
with the Holy Spirit of promise, it is the exact same word
used by John in Revelation 7
regarding the 144,000.
Now let's just think about it.
Why does this matter?
This seal protects and clearly identifies
who is part of the 144,000, correct?
Correct?
The Holy Spirit does that for us right here, right now.
Amen?
We ought to be easily identified as following Jesus
and belonging to Christ because the Holy Spirit's
fruit in our life is evident to all who see.
Listen, you should not have to ask if someone is spirit filled.
You should see it.
You should see it in the way they talk, and
the way they present themselves, and the way that they conduct business,
and the way that they handle their marriage and their children and
their finances, and their friendships, all the
things that we do in life, because we are sealed by
the promise of the holy or the Holy Spirit of promise, we
should be evident to all that we belong to God.
That's the seal.
Let's take it a step deeper here.
Jesus is teaching his disciples in Matthew 10.
He is telling them that because of their faith, they will be handed over before
governors in kings, right?
Listen to it right here.
Matthew 10, you can turn there if you want, but Matthew 10, 16 through 20.
Behold, I send you forth as sheep in the midst of wolves.
That sounds amazing, right?
Be ye therefore wise as serpents and harmless as doves.
Some of us just pick one and go with it.
It says both, amen?
You shouldn't you shouldn't be all snaky and
you shouldn't just be like a little dove.
We should be both.
We should be able to conduct ourselves in tension and conflict in
a godly way, but we should also be gentle.
Anyway, that's a whole nother message for another time.
But beware of men, for they will deliver you up to councils,
and they will scourge you in their synagogues, and ye shall be brought before governors
and kings for my sake for a testimony against them and the
Gentiles, but when they deliver you up.
Take no thought how or what ye shall speak, for it shall be
given you in the same hour, what you shall speak.
Has anyone ever had, um, uh, oh
man, I had the class.
I don't know what it's called now, speak like you
give speeches and stuff.
What is it called?
Speech?
It's public speaking.
Yeah, I had that, I had honors public speaking at
MTSU, man, I love that.
I love that stinging class.
And I, like, I could not wait to get up there and talk to my class, tell them how they're crazy.
But anyway, but listen, there's something here, when you,
if you go up and you're not confident, and you're not prepared,
what's that feeling like?
Let me ask you, if I just randomly started selecting people
to come and finish my message with my menu.
Hey, Evan, how you doing, bud?
Would you like to come up here and finish this message?
It's right there.
All you got to do is read it.
Listen, that's pretty difficult.
Tristan, hey man, how you doing tonight?
Would you like to come up here and read the message.
I can make the words bigger for some of you old folks.
Like, listen, I mean, your heart would drop, right?
So let's just think this for a second.
Let's times that by a million.
You're in front of a governor or a king or a jury or
whatever it is, and man, you got to give defense for yourself.
What is your preparation?
Your faith.
The Bible, now, listen, I'm not, I know he's speaking to disciples here.
I'm not trying to take this out of context.
But he promised the disciples, hey, don't worry about what to say.
The Holy Spirit that fills you will speak.
through you.
That's part of the seal.
That's part of that protected seal that we see.
For it is not ye that speak, but the spirit of your father which speaketh in you.
The guiding hand of the Holy Spirit is what we see here.
Well, what if we say the truth that the Spirit gives us and they still kill us?
What did they still imprison us?
Now, listen, I used to, when I 1st thought of preaching, I was like, man,
bring it on, bring me to jail.
Please don't bring me to jail.
Hey man, I don't want to go to jail.
That crazy young preacher acted like he wanted to go to jail.
I don't want to go to jail.
You know what I'm saying?
But what if it does happen?
Well, again, Jesus has words for that as well.
Matthew 10, just a few verses later, and fear
not them, which kill the body.
but are not able to kill the soul.
But rather fear him, which is able to destroy both soul and
body, in hell.
Church, listen, we may not make it out of line, but we will not die.
Did y'all like that?
We didn't put that somewhere.
We may not make it out alive, but we ain't gonna die.
Death for us is a momentary eye
closing just to open it to Jesus.
You understand what I'm saying?
2 Corinthians 5, 8.
We are of good courage, I say, and prefer rather to be absent from
the body and to be home with the Lord.
Philippians 121 for to me, to live as
Christ, and to die is gain.
How can you say that?
You got to be sealed.
There's no way you can say that and believe it unless you're sealed.
How do men and women get upon their knees before a loaded rifle or
a sharpened sword and not denounce Jesus?
The Holy Spirit has them sealed.
See, we think of this text as just for the disciples.
There's people being brought to whoever it
is in authority overseas and being told, hey,
you denounce Christ, we're going to take your life.
And I believe in that moment, the seal the Holy Spirit speaks through them and says,
Jesus is Lord.
And even though they're dead, They're alive in Christ.
Y'all with me, that's pretty cool right there.
I had this little pastor saying, if that doesn't get you fired up, your woods wet.
Okay, anyway.
And I said some old school stuff.
Now that was a fun and good truth rabbit, okay?
All right.
But let's go back to these 144,000.
There are 2 main interpretations of the identity of these sealed Jews.
Now remember, this is a teaching lesson, okay?
I know that was fun.
It was applicable, but we're gonna learn some stuff here.
Many of us are familiar, or maybe you're not, but
if when we say 144,000,
and you know anything about world religions, you instantly probably think
the Jehovah Witnesses and their perspective on the 144,000.
Their stance is that God is going to resurrect 144,000
to heaven as immortal spirits known as
the little flock, or the anointed ones, while the
rest of the witnesses will be on earth in paradise.
They call it the earthly hope.
Okay?
Um, Since this has no valid connection
to what the text says in any way, it is a false interpretation.
It should not be taken seriously in any manner.
We know for a fact, or
at least depending on the stance that you take, we'll talk about it too here, that
they have to be Jews.
You understand?
So that kind of takes some people out there.
But there are 2 main veins of interpretation here.
And it can be categorized in 2 thoughts.
You have a literal versus symbolic interpretation.
Now, again, this is not unique to the 144,000.
However, this particular topic is one of the
most argued, whether it is to be taken literal or symbolic.
The literal reading takes a futuristic reading.
There will be 144,000 actual
Jews who are sealed by God with an actual seal.
I believe it's the Holy Spirit.
I believe the whole, I know there's going to be something on their forehead, but I believe it's going to fill them with the Holy Spirit.
during a great tribulation in order to evangelize
the earth post-rapture and proclaim the gospel.
This makes sense once we know there will be those who are
saved in the great tribulation.
Well, how do they get saved if no one is sharing the gospel with them?
You understand what I'm saying?
Listen, hey, the Bible makes it very clear in Romans 10.
How can they believe unless they hear?
How can they hear unless, you know, they're sent, right?
And so we see here, that's what we are talking about.
Now, You have a symbolic approach.
This is a non-futuristic reading.
This sees the 144,000 as symbolic
of the church in totality.
In other words, that number is attached
to the fact that it's just a number, kind of like a placeholder,
but it represents, it symbolizes just the church as a whole.
Right?
Again, you got to think, you know, people think that we're going
to go through the tribulation.
There's a lot of different opinions on this.
The problem with this is that right after we learn about
the 144,000, we are also told about the great multitude.
Revelation 7, verse 9 through 17.
I want to read that to you.
And after this, I be held in lower great multitude, which no man
could number of all nations and kindreds and people and tongues,
stood before the throne and before the lamb, clothed in with
white robes and palms in their hands and cry with
a loud voice, saying, salvation to our God, which sitteth upon
the throne and to the lamb.
And all the angels stood round about the throne, and about the elders
and the 4 beasts, and fell before the throne on their faces, and worshiped God, saying, amen.
Blessing and glory and wisdom and thanksgiving and honor
and power and might be unto our God forever and ever.
Amen.
And then it says right here, and one of the elders answers, saying unto me, what
are these which are arrayed in white robes?
and whence came they?
In other words, who are these people?
And I said unto him, sir, thou knowest.
And he said unto me, these are they which came out of the
great tribulation and have washed their robes and made them white
in the blood of the lamb.
Therefore, are they before the throne of God and serve him
day and night in his temple, and he that sitteth on the throne shall dwell among them.
They shall hunger no more, neither thirst anymore, neither shall the
sun light on them, nor any heat for the lamb, which is in the midst
of the throne shall feed them, and shall lead them into the living fountains
of waters, and God shall wipe away all tears from their eyes.
Now, if you ask me, the way I read chapter
7, we see the sealed 144,000, then we see the result.
They're going out.
They're proclaiming the gospel.
They're protected and they're obvious of what their mission is.
And in the midst, they lead many to Christ.
Now.
John is specific that there is a number attached to the sealed
evangelist while the multitude cannot be numbered.
So they can't be the same people.
They can't be the same thing.
Also, the 144,000, specifically from
the tribes of the nation of Israel, while the multitude
is from every nation, and all tribes, and peoples, and tongues.
So in other words, there are 2 different groups mentioned here.
Now, I want to point out the last verse of this chapter in verse 17.
Look at it again.
For the lamb, which is in the midst of the throne, shall feed them and
shall lead them, unto living fountains of waters, and God
shall wipe away all tears from their eyes.
This is a great reminder that no matter what happens,
God is going to bring us to rest.
This is repeated in Revelation 21, verse 4, and God shall wipe
away all tears from their eyes.
And there should be no more death, neither sorrow nor crying, neither shall there
be any more pain for the former things are past.
away.
This is the endgame of God's eternal plan.
to bring creation back into right relationship eternally with him.
So before we get to the 7 trumpets, when God turns the heat up even
more through his wrath on the earth, let me ask you, what is your heart posture today?
Do you trust that God's plan is good and perfect?
The enemy has done a great job at distracting us in
thinking that the things that are not important are very important.
Now, what do I mean by that?
How many things on the news has this worried, angry and confused?
Think about how often we talk about politics rather than Jesus.
We look to a world system for peace and contentment while never
actually finding it because it's not there.
Social media is a peddler of lies and unrealistic expectation
that has an entire generation bound up
and rendered useless.
They're paralyzed with comparison.
They're paralyzed with with anxiety.
They're paralyzed with depression.
Why?
Because they're focusing on the wrong thing.
We've got the conspiracies one after the other.
Nothing is real.
Everything is gonna kill us.
World War 3 is on the way.
Guys, listen, I'm right there with you.
Your life changing when you start looking at ingredients on the back of your products.
Amen?
It's distracting.
What is that?
No one knows.
But I'm going to drink this drink anyway.
Amen.
You know what I'm saying?
It's distracting.
And we get so caught up in it.
We get so worried about it.
And in the meantime, we forget why we're here.
Realized 144,000, they are sealed in
the midst of the great tribulation.
They're not blind.
They see what's going on.
They're right there in the midst of it.
Yet God is protecting them.
Now, I'm not saying that you won't ever get sick.
I'm not saying that you won't ever have a crisis in your life.
I'm not saying that you're never going to have a bad day, but what I'm
going to say is the end goal of all of this.
is to rest in Christ.
And the Bible says we can start that today.
To make matters worse, there is the church who is split and fractured.
If we aren't fighting with the world, we're fighting with each other.
Do you see what the enemy is doing?
Creation is longing for its creator while we are worried about the issues we cannot control.
You must get focused on what matters.
The fight is not physical, but spiritual.
And God knew this.
Jesus knew that when he left his disciples, hard times would come.
That is why they're still, the Holy Spirit is so necessary.
In John 14, verse 26 and 27, it says,
but the comforter, which is the Holy Ghost, whom the Father will
send in my name, he shall teach you all things and bring all things to
your remembrance, whatsoever I have said unto you.
I know I read the scripture so much, but it's something that we need to be reminded of.
Verse 27, peace I leave with you.
My peace I give unto you, not as the world giveth.
The world can't give us what God gives us.
The world cannot replace the Holy Spirit.
There's many spirits in the world, but it's not the holy,
the Holy Spirit is within us.
God gave him to us.
Not as the world giveth, give eye unto you.
Let not your heart be troubled.
Neither let it be afraid.
Trust God's plan.
The world is going to be destroyed.
We know that.
He's going to make all things new.
Everything that is happening is simply set in the stage, but in the end,
after all the hurt, the pain, the death,
God is going to wipe the tears from our eyes.
If you've ever had kids, you understand it when a kid starts crying and they don't stop.
You know what I'm talking about?
And I tend to, unless there's a good reason to cry, I get irritated
quickly about the crime because it's just loud and obnoxious
and it's just like, just stop crying.
You know what I'm saying?
But there was one time I was trying to get real tender with my child.
And I'm not the most tender parent.
But I was trying to be tender in this moment.
And, uh, That's your time of going off.
That's crazy.
Anyway, I'm just kidding.
But, uh, and so she was crying and and, you know, I tried.
I tried the TBRI, you know what I'm saying?
I was trying to do what I should do as a parent.
And I got down to her level and I said, baby, there's no reason to cry anymore.
It's over.
And I wiped the tear from her eyes.
And I said, it's okay.
And I gave her a hug.
And you know what I did?
In that moment?
Listen, it may never happen again.
But in that moment, it's almost like, it's almost like because I'm her daddy.
And she can trust me that it's okay.
I'm here.
I'm protecting you.
It over.
It's done with, you don't have to worry about that anymore.
As I wiped away her tears, I wiped away the problem.
I want you to know something.
My kids since then has cried.
Right?
I'm just going to let you know.
But when God wipes away our tears.
We'll never have a knee to cry again.
No pain.
No sorrow.
No cancer,
No sickness, no disease.
No family issues that hurt.
would just be with Jesus.
Boom.
That was such a tender moment.
But all I'm trying to say tonight is trust this plan.
Just this plan.
It has been us close over this place.